motorhomefacts.com 2013-09-11

# UK Motorhomes, Motorhome Information, Motorhomes Reviews, American RV Reviews, Motorhome Forum, American RV forum, Sales, Campsites ->Motorhome Sales

**Motorhome Facts** is the sole owner of the information collected from our website. We do not, or will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in our privacy statement below.

 ** _Cookies_**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Advertisers connected to **Motorhome Facts** at times require cookies to tract statistics about products and locations, but at no time are these linked to any personal identification. At this time, **Motorhome Facts** uses cookies only for login convenience.

 ** _Log Files_**  
 **Motorhome Facts** keeps log files on broad fields to analyze trends, track user movements, and gather data for demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitor's personal identification.

 ** _Sharing_**  
At this time, **Motorhome Facts** does not share any information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.

 ** _Links_**  
Links to other sites outside of **Motorhome Facts** do not apply to this privacy statement. We are not responsible for privacy policies of other websites linked to **Motorhome Facts**. Please read the privacy statement of each website linked to **Motorhome Facts** for information and data use for visitor's personal identification. Our privacy statement applies solely to **Motorhome Facts**.

 ** _Contests_**  
At any particular time, **Motorhome Facts** will conduct contests for our visitor's. Visitor participation for these contests is voluntary, and in no way requires the visitor to give out personal information when choosing not to enter in the contest. Collected information may include contact information and demographic information, such as name, e-mail, address, state, ect. This information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.

 ** _Newsletter_**  
After registering for a Membership, you are given the choice of subscribing to our Newsletter. You can either elect to subscribe or unsubscribe at any time. All information stored on our database is not shared or sold to any third party what so ever. Subscribers wishing to unsubscribe to our newsletter can uncheck the option in their account, using the 'Your Information' link.

 ** _Sending to a Friend_**  
When a visitor chooses to send News, Articles, Reviews, ect, to a friend, the names and e-mail addresses are **not** logged. **Motorhome Facts** will send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit our site. **Motorhome Facts** will never send another e-mail to the visitor or friend for any purpose.

 ** _Changes of our Policy_**  
If and when our policy statement changes, visitors with Memberships in our databases will be notified of the changes, and provided a link to this page to view the changes. If a visitor decides that our policy does not benefit them, they can use the opt-out option at anytime.
